Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- P
  - Petal Paper Place of publication: Montgomery/Petal, Ala./Miss. Publisher: Southeastern Publishing Col., 1962-1972 (Box 337)
  - PFLP Bulletin Place of publication: Beirut Publisher: PFLP International Relations Committee, 1972?-1982 (Box 319)
  - Philadelphia Free Press Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa., 1969-1973 (Box 337)
  - Philadelphia Worker Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa., 1975 (Box 487)
  - Philly Facts Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia-TWU Local 234, 1945 (Box 411)
  - Phoenix Place of publication: Nashville, Tenn. Publisher: Southern Student Organizing Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 338)
  - Phoenix Facts Place of publication: Phoenix, Ariz. Publisher: Education Committee of 8560, CWA, 1985 (Box 115C)
  - Picket Line Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: L.A.-Student-Worker Action Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 338)
  - Pitirre Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Young Lords Organization, 1969-1970 (Box 338)
  - Plain Dealer Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa., 1970 (Box 338)
  - Plain Rapper Place of publication: Palo Alto, Calif. Publisher: Palo Alto Resistance, 1969 (Box 338)
  - Plain Speaking: A News Journal of the Democratic Workers Party Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Democratic Workers Party, 1977-1982 (Box 338)
  - Plain Talk Place of publication: Salt Lake City, Utah Publisher: Plain Talk Publishing Association, 1910 (Box 338)
  - Plexus Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Prism Pub., 1974-1979 (Box 338)
  - PM Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Newspaper PM, 1940 (Box 339)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7021)
  - Point of Production Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Black Workers Congress, 1972 (Box 338)
  - Point of Production Place of publication: Gary, Ind. Publisher: Black Workers Congress, 1971-1972 (Box 357)
  - Le Populaire de Paris Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Parti Socialiste SFIO, 1968 (Box 338)
  - Portland Alliance, The Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: Oregon Coalition of Alternative Human Services (Box 5)
  - Por la paz y la solidaridad Place of publication: Oakland, Calif., 1987 (Box 139)
  - Positive View Place of publication: Sacramento, Calif. Publisher: Communications Workers of America, Local 9421, 1985 (Box 115C)
  - Post American Place of publication: Deerfield, N.Y. Publisher: People's Christian Coalition, 1971 (Box 340)
  - Post-Amerikan Place of publication: Bloomington, Ill., 1981-1984 (Box 340)
  - Postal Workers Voice: National Rank & File Newspaper Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Rank & File Committee, 1977 (Box 340)
  - Postmark Washington Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National Association of Letter Carriers, 1985-1988 (Box 488)
  - Potomac Alliance Power Plant Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Potomac Alliance, 1980 (Box 340)
  - Pouvoir Ouvrier Place of publication: Paris, France, 1967?-1969 (Box 435)
  - Poverty Law Report Place of publication: Montgomery, Ala. Publisher: Southern Poverty Law Center, 1974-1979 (Box 340)
  - Prairie Fire Place of publication: Saskatchewan, Canada Publisher: Regina Community Media Project, 1970-1971 (Box 340)
  - ¡Presente! Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: SOA Watch, 2008 (Box 343)
  - Prisoners Solidarity Committee Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1971 (Box 342)
  - Programma comunista Place of publication: Milan, Italy Publisher: Partito Comunista Internazionale, 2006-current (Box 343)
  - The Progressive Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: National Postal Union, 1959-1971 (Box 344)
  - Progressive Citizen Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Progressive Citizens of America, 1948 (Box 344)
  - Progressive Labor Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Progressive Labor Party, 1982-1983 (Box 343)
  - Progressive Painter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Inter-Local Conference of Progressive Painters, 1938-1967 (Box 343)
  - Progressive Populist Place of publication: Storm Lake, Iowa Publisher: Ampersand Publishing Company, 2002-2003 (Box 344)
  - Progressive Student News Place of publication: Iowa City, Iowa Publisher: Progressive Student Network, 1988-1989 (Box 343)
  - Progressive Woman Place of publication: Middlebury, Ind. Publisher: Corson Pub., 1972 (Box 344)
  - Proletären Place of publication: Göteborg, Sweden Publisher: KPML(r), 1997 (Box 340)
  - Le Proletaire Place of publication: Marseille, France Publisher: Parti Communiste Internationale, 1969-1983 (Box 343)
  - Proletarische Aktion Place of publication: Zurich, Switzerland, 1948 (Box 343)
  - Protean/Radish Place of publication: Chapel Hill, N.C., 1969-1970 (Box 343)
  - Protos Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Underground Press Syndicate, 1970-1971 (Box 343)
  - Providence Free Press Place of publication: Providence, R.I., nd (Box 343)
  - Provincial Press Collective Place of publication: Spokane, Wash., 1970-1972 (Box 343)
  - Psychologists for a Democratic Society Newspaper Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: PDS, 1968-1969 (Box 343)
  - Public Place of publication: Urbana-Champaign, Ill. Publisher: Urbana-Champaign Independent Media Center, 2002 (Box 345)
  - Public Citizen Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Public Citizen, Inc., 1976-1982 (Box 343)
  - Public Employee Place of publication: Ottawa, Canada Publisher: Public Relations Dept. of the Canadian Union of Public Employees, 1978-1979 (Box 345)
  - Public Employee: Official Publication, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Place of publication: Mount Morris, Ill. Publisher: AFSCME, 1969-1985 (Box 345-346)
  - Public Employee Press Place of publication: N.Y. Publisher: District Council 37, American Federation of State and Municipal Employees, 1966-current (Box 347-356A)
  - The Public Life Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1968-1970 (Box 347)
  - The Public Record Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Workers of America, 1950-1952 (Box 487)
  - Pulp Place of publication: Amherst, Mass., 1971 (Box 347)
  - Pulp and Paper Worker Place of publication: Fort Edward, N.Y. Publisher: Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1968 (Box 320)
- Q
  - Quantum: An Independent Marxist Newspaper Place of publication: Aberdeen, S.D., 1972 (Box 248)
  - Quash Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Grand Jury Project, 1975-1983 (Box 347)
  - Quatrieme Internationale Publisher: Parti Communiste Internationaliste, 1965-1966 (Box 436)
  - Queen City Express Publisher: Cincinnati, Ohio, 1970 (Box 437)
  - Quepasa Place of publication: Syracuse, N.Y., 1976-1978 (Box 347)
  - Quicksilver Times Place of publication: U.S.A., 1969 (Box 477)
- R
  - Radical Therapist Place of publication: West Sommerville, Mass. Publisher: Radical Therapist, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 402)
  - The Rag Place of publication: Austin, Tex., 1970-1971 (Box 357A)
  - Rage Place of publication: Jacksonville, N.C. Publisher: By and for Marines from Camp Lejeune, 1971-1974 (Box 164)
  - Rainbow People Place of publication: Gresham, Or., nd (Box 357A)
  - Railroad Workers' Link Place of publication: N.Y. Publisher: Communist Party of the U.S. of A. New York (State) Railroad Committee, 1948 (Box 359)
  - Rake Place of publication: Providence, R.I. Publisher: Rake Collective, 1989 (Box 357A)
  - Rally, Comrades! Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Central Committee of the Communist Labor Party of the United States of North America, 1981-1995 (Box 357A, 358)
  - Rand School News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Rand School of Social Science, 1918-1924 (Box 357)
  - Rank and File Advocate Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: New Directions/TWU 100, 2002-2005 (Box 357A)
  - Rank & File Unity Place of publication: Beckley, W. Va. Publisher: Miners' Right to Strike Committee, 1977 (Box 359)
  - Rank & File Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Publicity and Newsletter Committee of the Rank and File Labor Coalition, 1980-1981 (Box 357A)
  - Rap! Place of publication: Columbus, Ga., 1970-1971 (Box 164)
  - La Rassemblement Place of publication: Paris, France, 1948 (Box 359)
  - Rat, nd (Box 477)
  - The Rat Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: R.A.T. Publications, Inc., 1970-1972 (Box 357A-357B)
  - Rat Subterranean News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: R.A.T. Publications, Inc., 1968-1969 (Box 357A-357B)
  - La Raza Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: La Raza, 1970? (Box 97)
  - La Razón Place of publication: Amsterdam, Netherlands Publisher: C.N.T/A.I.T, 1977 (Box 28)
  - Rebel Place of publication: London?, England Publisher: YS (Box 436)
  - Rebellion! Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Progressive Labor Party, 1991 (Box 359)
  - Rebellion News Place of publication: Boston, Mass., 1967-1968 (Box 359)
  - Rebirth Place of publication: Phoenix, Ariz. Publisher: Real Live People, 1969 (Box 359)
  - The Record Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NY ITU Local 6, 1963 (Box 359)
  - Red Balloon Place of publication: Stony Brook, N.Y. Publisher: Red Balloon Collective, 1976-1985 (Box 359)
  - Red Bass Place of publication: Tallahassee, Fla. Publisher: Red Bass Productions, 1986 (Box 357)
  - Red Earth Place of publication: U.S.A., nd (Box 359)
  - Red Flag Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Revolutionary Workers Party, 1963-1966 (Box 359)
  - Red Flag Place of publication: Hollywood, Calif. Publisher: Red Flag Union, 1977 (Box 359)
  - Red Flag: Organ of the Marxist League Place of publication: London, England, 1937 (Box 359)
  - Red Front Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Executive Board, Red Front, 1933 (Box 359)
  - Red Menace Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Toronto Libertarian School, 1976-1979 (Box 359)
  - Red Pencil Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Boston Area Teaching Project, Inc., 1972 (Box 359)
  - Red Sky, Blue Sky Place of publication: Mich. Publisher: Mt. Pleasant Anarchist Group, 1970 (Box 359)
  - Red Star Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: The Women's Detachment, 1971 (Box 238)
  - Red Star Place of publication: Mosinee, Wis., 1950 (Box 512)
  - Red Star Express Place of publication: Milwaukee, Wis. Publisher: Revolutionary Youth Movement, 1970 (Box 359)
  - Red Times Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Detroit Youth Against War and Fascism, 1970-1971 (Box 359)
  - Red Weekly Place of publication: London, England Publisher: International Marxist Group, 1973-1976 (Box 360)
  - Réfractaire Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: May Picqueray, 1982 (Box 206)
  - Rejoice Place of publication: Las Vegas, Nev. Publisher: Trinity Temple, nd (Box 206)
  - Report / National Steelworkers Rank and File Committee Place of publication: Lorain, Ohio Publisher: National Steelworkers Rank and File Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 359)
  - Report on El Salvador Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Religious Task Force on El Salvador, 1980 (Box 359)
  - Reporter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Legislative Conference of the City University of New York, 1971 (Box 487)
  - Resistance Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: New England Resistance, 1968 (Box 360)
  - Resistance Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Friends of Durruti, 1984-1988 (Box 360)
  - Resistance = Resistencia Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: League for Proletarian Revolution, 1976 (Box 371)
  - Resistance: Journal of the North American Earth Liberation Front Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: North American Earth Liberation Front Press Office (Box 359)
  - Resistance News / National Resistance Committee Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: National Resistance Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 360)
  - Resistencia Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Resistencia Puertorriqueña, 1976 (Box 360)
  - Restaurant Employee Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Local 1, 1979 (Box 360)
  - Resurrection: People's News Service Place of publication: Tucson, Ariz. Publisher: Ministry of Information, 1970 (Box 248)
  - Revolt Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Revolt Publishing Association, 1916 (Box 360)
  - Révoltes Place of publication: Paris, France, 1966-1968 (Box 360)
  - Revolution Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Revolutionary Union/Revolutionary Communist Party, 1973-current (Box 360-361C)
  - Revolution Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: CUNY Revolutionary Reconstruction and Internationalist Clubs, 2003-current (Box 361)
  - Revolutionary Age Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Left Wing Section of the Socialist Party, 1919 (Box 510)
    Researchers must use reprint volumes or microfilm (Film R-7792)
  - Revolutionary Cause Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: August 29th Movement, 1975-1978 (Box 361)
  - Revolutionary Communist Youth / Revolutionary Communist Youth Brigade Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Youth Brigade, 1978-1982 (Box 362)
  - Revolutionary Communist Youth Newsletter Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1970-1973 (Box 498)
  - Revolutionary Student Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American Student Movement (Anti-Imperialist), 1971 (Box 238)
  - Revolutionary Worker Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: RCP Publications, 1979-2005 (Box 363-371)
  - Revolutionary Worker (NY/NJ edition) Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist Party, USA, 1979 (Box 371)
  - Revolutionary Youth Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Revolutionary Youth League, 1978 (Box 371)
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement Newsletter Place of publication: Racine, Wis. Publisher: Revolutionary Youth Movement, nd (Box 371)
  - Richmond Chronicle Place of publication: Richmond, Va., 1970 (Box 371)
  - The RICOSH Quarterly / Rhode Island Committee on Occupational Safety and Health Place of publication: Providence, R.I. Publisher: Rhode Island Committee on Occupational Safety and Health, 1980-2012 (Box 30)
  - Riff Raff Place of publication: Paris, France, 1994 (Box 372)
  - Right on Time: The Revolutionary Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: CFC: A Collective of Liberation Centers, 1973-1974 (Box 371)
  - Right On!: Black Community News Service Place of publication:Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: Black Panther Party, 1971-1972 (Box 373)
  - Rights of Man Place of publication: New Orleans, La. Publisher: GROW Project of the Southern Conference Educational Fund, Inc., 1969?-1969 (Box 372)
  - Rising Up Angry Place of publication: Chicago, Ill., 1969-1975 (Box 372)
  - Rochester Patriot Place of publication: Rochester, N.Y., 1981 (Box 373)
  - Rochester's People's Paper Place of publication: Rochester, Mich., nd (Box 372)
  - Rock Creek Free Press Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: M. Sullivan, 2007-2011 (Box 371)
  - Rodan Place of publication: Calif. Publisher: Northern California Asian American Community, 1971 (Box 372)
  - Ronin, nd (Box 31)
  - Roosevelt Torch Place of publication: Roosevelt, 1970 (Box 372)
  - Rouge Place of publication: Paris, France, 1969-1987 (Box 373-373A)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7222)
  - Rough Times Place of publication: West Sommerville, Mass. Publisher: Radical Therapist, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 402)
  - RPM Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Detroit Organizing Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 347)
  - RT: A Journal of Radical Therapy Place of publication: West Sommerville, Mass. Publisher: Radical Therapist, Inc., 1974-1976 (Box 402)
  - RWDSU Record Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1996-2000 (Box 30)
- S
  - S.C.A.R.'(d) Times Place of publication: Portland, Me. Publisher: New England Prisoners Association, 1973 (Box 342)
  - Sabot Place of publication: Seattle, Wash., 1971 (Box 374)
  - SACC Newsletter Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: MIT Science Action Coordinating Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 374)
  - Salt of the Earth Place of publication: San Jose, Calif., 1971 (Box 374)
  - Samasamajist Place of publication: Colombo, Sri Lanka Publisher: Lanka Samasamaja Party, 1957-1960 (Box 436)
  - San Diego Feminist Communications Place of publication: San Diego, Calif. Publisher: San Diego Feminist Communications, 1975-1978 (Box 374)
  - San Francisco Express Times Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Trystero Co., 1968 (Box 374)
  - San Jose Red Eye Place of publication: San Jose, Calif. Publisher: Red Eye Media, 1970-1971 (Box 374)
  - Sanity Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Campaign for Nuclear Disarmament, 1972 (Box 196)
  - Save Our Jobs News / Wisconsin Steelworkers Place of publication: [Chicago, Ill.] Publisher: Wisconsin Steelworkers, 1985 (Box 374)
  - Sawt Alitihad Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Iraqi Democratic Union, 1982-nd (Box 374)
  - Screen Actor News Hollywood Place of publication: Hollywood, Calif. Publisher: Screen Actors Guild, 1975-1986 (Box 374)
  - Sea Notes Place of publication: Elizabeth, N.J. Publisher: Sea-Land Service, Inc., 1972-nd (Box 375)
  - The Sea Turtle and the Shark Place of publication: U.S.A., 1970 (Box 374)
  - Seafarers Log Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Seafarers International Union, Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes, and Inland Waters District, AFL-CIO, 1949-1969 (Box 375)
  - Seafarers Log Place of publication: Camp Springs, Md. Publisher: Seafarers International Union, Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes and Inland Waters District, 1988-current (Box 378-381B)
  - Seattle Semi Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Teamster Rank and File Monthly, 1972-1975 (Box 375)
  - Second City Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. (Box 375)
  - Second Coming Place of publication: Ypsilanti, Mich., 1969-1971 (Box 375)
  - The Second Page Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1971-1972 (Box 477)
  - Seed Place of publication: Chicago, Ill., 1969-1972 (Box 388A-388B)
  - Semper Fi Place of publication: Iwakuni, Japan Publisher: GIs at MCAS Iwakuni, 1972 (Box 164)
  - Senior Citizens News Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National Council of Senior Citizens, 1963 (Box 375)
  - Service Employee Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Service Employee International Union, 1971-1987 (Box 382-383)
  - Servir le peuple Publisher: Groupes de Travail Communistes et l'Union des Jeunesses Communistes, 1968 (Box 382)
  - The Sextant Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1946-1961 (Box 384B)
  - The Shadow Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Shadow Press, 1989-2008 (Box 028A)
  - Shakedown Place of publication: Wrightstown, N.J. Publisher: Ft. Dix G.I.s, 1969-1970 (Box 164)
  - The Sheepshead Bay Township Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y., 1971-1972 (Box 384B)
  - Shelter Place of publication: Kansas City, Mo., 1971?-1972 (Box 384B)
  - Shelterforce Place of publication: East Orange, N.J. Publisher: Shelterforce Collective, 1975-1985 (Box 384B)
  - Sherwood Forest Place of publication: Irvine, Calif. Publisher: Orange County People's Press, nd (Box 384A)
  - Shift-change: The Newspaper of the New York Taxi Workers Alliance Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Taxi Workers Alliance, 2011-current (Box 416)
  - Short Times Place of publication: Columbia, S.C. Publisher: GIs United Against the War in Vietnam, 1969-1971 (Box 164)
  - Sí se puede Place of publication: Santa Barbara, Calif. Publisher: Congreso, UCSB, 1976-1977 (Box 395)
  - Siege Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Black Workers Congress, 1971-1972 (Box 384B)
  - Sister: West Coast Feminist Newspaper Place of publication: Venice, Calif., 1973-1979 (Box 374)
  - Skilled Tradesman Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Independent Skilled Trades Council (UAW), 1975-1980 (Box 388)
  - Slingshot Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: ASUC sponsored, 1998-current (Box 384A)
  - Small Arms Place of publication: Springfield, Mass., nd (Box 477)
  - Smoke Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich., 1973 (Box 384A)
  - SNCC Newsletter Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga. Publisher: Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, 1967 (Box 512)
  - Socialist Action Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich., 1973 (Box 384)
  - Socialist Action Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: [Socialist Party of the United States of America. National Headquarters], 1935 (Box 384A)
  - Socialist Action Place of publication: Wellington, New Zealand, 1970-1971 (Box 436)
  - Socialist Action / City Workers Committee of The League for the Revolutionary Party Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: City Workers Committee of the League for the Revolutionary Party, 1976-1980 (Box 384A)
  - Socialist Appeal Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Trotskyist Organizing Committee, nd (Box 436)
  - Socialist Current Place of publication: London, England, 1968-1972 (Box 384B)
  - Socialist Leader Place of publication: London, England, 1949-1969 (Box 384B)
  - Socialist Organiser Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Socialist Organiser, 1986-1990 (Box 487)
  - Socialist Organiser Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Alliance for Workers' Liberty, 1985-1993 (Box 488-490)
  - Socialist Organiser Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Socialist Organiser, 1991-1993 (Box 489)
  - Socialist Tribune Place of publication: Milwaukee, Wis. Publisher: Socialist Tribune, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 382)
  - Socialist Voice Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: League for the Revolutionary Party, 1977-1978 (Box 389)
  - Socialist Worker Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: International Socialist Organization, 1977-current (Box 389-394B)
  - De Soldatenkrant Place of publication: Amsterdam, Netherlands Publisher: Bond voor Dienstplichtigen, 1974 (Box 395)
  - The Soledad Brothers Place of publication: Calif., 1971 (Box 342)
  - Solidaridad Publisher: A.I.T., 1961 (Box 395)
  - Solidaridad obrera Place of publication: Barcelona, Spain Publisher: Las Sociedades Obreras, 1907 (Box 28)
  - Solidaridad obrera: órgano de la Confederación Regional del Trabajo de Cataluña: portavoz de la Confederación Nacional del Trabajo de España Place of publication: Barcelona, Spain Publisher: CNT-AIT, Comité Regional de Catalunya, 2007 (Box 28)
  - Solidaridad obrera: supplemento literario Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: C.N.T. d'Espagne en exil, 1959 (Box 28)
  - Solidarity Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: N.Y. S.D.S. Labor Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 261)
  - Solidarity / International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Implement Workers of America - UAW Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: UAW, 1966-1976 (Box 438)
  - Solidarity Newsletter / Philadelphia Solidarity Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia Solidarity, 1972-1976? (Box 395)
  - Soul Force Place of publication: Atlanta, Ga. Publisher: Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1970-1971 (Box 395)
  - The South End Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Wayne State University, 1969 (Box 38)
  - South Manhattan Peace and Freedom Report Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1969 (Box 325)